https://www.zones.com/site/statics/static_page.html?name=corporate/terms-and-conditions/privacy-policy

General Policies
Terms and Conditions
General Policies
Privacy Policy
Zones, LLC, ("Zones" or "we") a global IT solutions provider, delivers products and services to help companies make a complete digital transformation – from desktop to data center – to the cloud and beyond. Zones is committed to Customer privacy. We regularly review our privacy policies to ensure we remain current with applicable laws, as well as ensuring the goodwill of our Customers.
This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") explains how Zones and its affiliates collect, retain, use, disclose, or otherwise process information about our Customers and potential customers (each, a "Customer", or "You").
INFORMATION RETAINED OR COLLECTED BY ZONES
Information that You Provide to Zones
Zones retains information that Customers provide in association with business transactions, such as name, address, billing information, shipping addresses, phone number, email address, credit card information, etc. ("Transactional Information"). Zones may also retain certain other information that you provide, including names and email addresses associated with email subscriptions, surveys, requested quotes, or other registration activities ("Other Customer Information"). Transactional Information and Other Customer Information are collectively referred to herein as "Customer Information".
Cookies and Web Logs
Zones aggregates cookies, IP addresses, and web log data associated with website visitors to help us understand how best to serve Customers. We also may utilize such data in conjunction with a Customer's shopping cart and/or registration to make appropriate product, service, and solution recommendations.
Third Party Tracking Software
Zones may use third party tracking software to gather information about where users are coming from and how they are using our site. This data is collected and used in an aggregated form to evaluate Zones' website performance and marketing program effectiveness.
HOW ZONES USES CUSTOMER INFORMATION
Zones may use Transactional Information to complete and satisfy orders and/or to contact Customers about their orders or registration when necessary.
Zones also may use Transactional Information to deliver promotional offers through email and postal mail and may occasionally share Customer names and postal addresses with reputable third parties that offer products and services related to individual Customers' interests. This activity can be cancelled at any time by a Customer following the instructions set forth under "Opting Out" below.
Zones uses opt-in email registration to deliver promotional offers through email. We use profile information you provide to tailor offers of potential interest to you. This profile data is held on a secure server and is not distributed to third parties for marketing purposes.
If a Customer volunteers to participate in a Zones survey, the information provided is held on a secure server. This information is analyzed at an aggregate level and used to help Zones improve its business practices and customer service.
In some cases, Zones may provide to its subcontractor certain among a Customer's Transactional Information so that such subcontractor can provide services to that specific Customer. All Zones contracts with subcontractors require them to maintain the confidentiality and security of Customer information and to use it only for the purpose of delivering the products and/or services for which they were contracted.
Zones' websites may contain links to other sites. While Zones seeks to promote sound privacy policies with all of its partners, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of entities whose websites are accessed via such links. Zones suggests that Customers review the privacy policies of all websites before providing any personal information to them.
In extreme cases, where and when required by law or by governmental or judicial authority, Zones may be required to release Customer information to authorities in the event of credit card fraud, illegal internet use, unauthorized use or acts committed in connection with this site, or other criminal or unauthorized activity.
SECURITY AND PROTECTION
Zones makes commercially reasonable efforts to store and protect Customer Information from loss, illegal access, misuse, and destruction. Additionally, we store all Customer Information on a secure server and limit access to Customer Information to authorized personnel.
OPTING OUT
Zones may use Customer Information to contact Customers about new products and services, special promotions, exclusive offers, or upcoming events. Any U.S. person may request such person's removal from Zones' marketing, mailing, and emailing lists by sending, as applicable, such person's first name, last name, address and zip code or email address to the following:
Zones' Customer Service
Toll-Free Phone: (800) 248-9948
Email: customerservice@zones.com
Hours: M-F: 6 a.m. to 5 p.m. PST
Any request for removal, as set forth above, shall be granted and promptly acted upon by Zones.
Any EU residents requesting removal should contact our Information Security Team at the following email address: Informationsecurity@zones.com
CHILDREN
Zones' websites are not intended or designed for use by children under the age of 13. To comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, children under 13 should not provide us with any personal information online. We strongly urge parents to supervise their children's online activity.
CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY
Zones reserves the right to amend or update this Privacy Policy at any time. Any updates or amendments to this Privacy Policy will be posted on this page and shall apply from the time of such posting.
ACCESS TO CUSTOMER INFORMATION
Customers have online access to their own Customer Information retained by Zones. Additional access to Customer Information is available during Zones' regular business hours. Customers may contact Zones via the information below to review, update, or inquire about their information.
Zones, LLC
1102 15th St SW, Ste 102
Auburn, WA 98001
Toll-Free Phone: (833) 681-0341
Or feel free to utilize our complete Contact List.
CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
Subject to certain limitations, California law permits California residents to request certain information regarding our collection or disclosure of personal information during the preceding calendar year. To make such a request, California residents can write to us at dataprivacy@zones.com, Attn: CCPA Data Request, and include your name and the address to which you would like us to respond. You can also call us toll-free at (833) 681-0341.
Last Updated: December 31, 2019
Solutions
Journals
Resources
Zones Blog
General
Policies
Terms
